<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lab member on NoCE Lab</title><link>https://noce-lab.github.io/tags/lab-member/</link><description>Recent content in lab member on NoCE Lab</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 18:23:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://noce-lab.github.io/tags/lab-member/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bonjour! I'm Marion</title><link>https://noce-lab.github.io/posts/introductions/mb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 18:23:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noce-lab.github.io/posts/introductions/mb/</guid><description>Bonjour, I’m Marion. I studied in Liège in Belgium. I have a Bachelor’s degree in general psychology and a Master’s degree in cognitive neuroscience. During my PhD, I studied the interaction between language and working memory using both a behavioral and a neuroimaging approach. Then, after all these years in Liège, I discovered new horizons after I was given the opportunity to be a research assistant in Fribourg, Switzerland, where I continued studying the interactions between working memory and language.</description></item><item><title>Hi! I'm Abigail</title><link>https://noce-lab.github.io/posts/introductions/al/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 18:23:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noce-lab.github.io/posts/introductions/al/</guid><description>I’m a PhD student in neuroscience (LNDS) researching cross-linguistic influence on semantic knowledge in multilingualism. During my bachelor’s in neuroscience (University of Cincinnati) I investigated sound symbolism and cognition-emotion interactions in reading. I completed my master’s degree in neuro-cognitive psychology in Munich, Germany (LMU) where I examined language and cognitive performance alongside PET imaging in patients with primary progressive aphasia. After my master’s degree, I moved to San Francisco, California (UCSF) to work as a neuroimaging data assistant and to gain knowledge of multimodal imaging techniques for the visualization of neuroanatomical changes related to language dysfunction.</description></item><item><title>Ciao! I am Valentina</title><link>https://noce-lab.github.io/posts/introductions/vb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 07:37:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noce-lab.github.io/posts/introductions/vb/</guid><description>After a bachelor’s degree in experimental psychology (UNIBO), a master’s in neuropsychology (UNITN), and a Ph.D. in cognitive neuroscience (UPMC), I perfected my unique combination of skills and knowledge with postdoctoral work in both clinical neuroscience (UCSF) and computational neuroscience (UdeM) neuroscience.
My research interest, a multidimensional investigation of the neuro-cognitive interplay of semantic knowledge and language, requires leveraging a wide array of techniques across different disciplines including neuropsychology, cognitive neuroimaging, and computer science.</description></item></channel></rss>