<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>outreach on NoCE Lab</title><link>https://noce-lab.github.io/tags/outreach/</link><description>Recent content in outreach on NoCE Lab</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:37:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://noce-lab.github.io/tags/outreach/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SNL 2023: Exploring Language Neuroscience</title><link>https://noce-lab.github.io/posts/outreach/snl2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:37:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noce-lab.github.io/posts/outreach/snl2023/</guid><description>Abigail, Sarah and Marion participated in SNL 2023 in Marseille!
SNL2023 was a blast! Three days filled with amazing discussions led by renowned experts in various fields of language neuroscience.
Opening Presentation by Jean-Rémi King The grand event commenced with a captivating presentation by Jean-Rémi King, where the audience was introduced to cutting-edge computational projects created by Meta. He presented their recent work entitled &amp;ldquo;The Unreasonable Effectiveness of AI in Neurosciences&amp;rdquo; (a reference to physicist Wigner’s 1960 work), where researchers trained artificial intelligence (AI) to decode MEG signals in response to images.</description></item><item><title>Scientifica: Switzerland's Premier Science Festival</title><link>https://noce-lab.github.io/posts/outreach/scientifica/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 07:37:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://noce-lab.github.io/posts/outreach/scientifica/</guid><description>Since 2011, Switzerland has been home to Scientifica, the country&amp;rsquo;s largest science festival, co-hosted by ETH Zurich and the University of Zurich. Held every two years with a unique theme for each edition, Scientifica has consistently drawn over 20,000 visitors. This event provides an exceptional platform for researchers to engage the public through a wide array of activities, including exhibitions and workshops.
Highlights from Scientifica23 In the most recent Scientifica event, Scientifica23, the NoCE lab was one of the booths representing the NCCR Evolving Language project.</description></item></channel></rss>